CURRICULAM VITAE

S. JAYASUDHA - B.Com, M.Com

10/794 JJ Nagar Mugappair East

Chennai 600 037

MOBILE: 9677292892

EMAIL ID: jayasudha.7519@gmail.com

Career Objective

To be associated with a progressive organization that gives me the scope to apply my knowledge and skills, involve myself as a part of the team that works dynamically towards the growth of the organization and expose myself to a continuous learning experience.

Experience:

Jan 2018 to till date

Sr. Accountant

Intact Fit Private Limited

Shenoy Nagar – Chennai

Intact Fit Pvt Ltd is a Master franchisee of "Levi Strauss (India) Pvt Ltd" and "Celio Future Fashion Pvt Ltd" Head office in Chennai and branches in Karnataka, Pondicherry and Kerala. Retail Seller of Readymade Garments.

Roles & Responsibilities:-

- Preparing reports and filing GSTR1 & GSTR3B.
- Monthly Reconciliation of GST receivables & Payables.
- Preparing reports for GSTR Annual Return GSTR9 & GSTR9C
- Preparing report for TDS return perodically.
- Paying and filing of TDS return "Saral TDS software".
- Updating lower TDS rate and maintaining the report for the same.
- Issuing of necessary forms, Form 16A, Form 16 etc.
- Preparing Salary Statement and disbursing salary to all the employees in 4 branches.
- Making satuatory payments like PF, ESI, GST, PT and Advance Tax.
- Co-ordinating with the auditors and the consultants in all four states towards statutory compliances like GST, trade licence, form 5 etc.
- Liasing with financial institution and bank for the purpose of arranging term loan, over drafts etc
- Reconciliation of accounting ledgers with corresponding documents, statements, etc.,
- Co-ordinating and handling Internal audit and statutory audit requirements
- Working on bank reconciliation statement, Customer and Vendors ledger reconciliation.
- Preparing and checking of bank and cash reconciliation, Pending entries, Ledger entries etc.
- Preparing cheques and doing online transactions like NEFT & RTGS
- Making online telephone payments
- Posting Sale, Purchase, Payment, Receipt, contra & Journal Entries in Tally.
- Making branch to branch entries in tally.
- Preparing EWaybill for stock transfer.
- Preparing reports for auditing purpose.
- Updating bank & doing BRS on daily basis.
- Preparing cheques and maintaining PDC Cheques and allocating fund for its clearance.

Feb 2013 to Jan 2018 Accountant Pyro Safe Private Lmited Padi - Chennai

PYRO SAFE Private Limited, (PSPL) is one of the leading EPC Contractors for Fire Fighting System, Utility Piping System & Fire Alarm System Provider for Industrial, Commercial and Residential establishments in the country.

Roles & Responsibilities:-

- Working in Tally ERP 9 (Latest Version 6.2)Software
- Reading mail on daily basis and responding to it accordingly.
- Handling pettycash & Checking BRS
- Preparing cheques and doing online transactions like NEFT & RTGS
- Preparing advance & performance bank guarantees
- Preparing Bank Balance Statement
- Maintaining PDC Cheques
- Planning Fund Flow
- Reconciling Suppliers & Contractors Bills
- Handling creditors payables & follow up of debtors receivables
- Preparing stock and debtors statement for bank OD / CC A/c
- Posting sales, purchase, payments, receipts, journal and contra entries in Tally
- Reading, monitoring and responding to the email
- Praparing Bills for various sites and following the same
- Following up with Sites for Day-to-Day information, Sub-Contractors details, work orders, Cash Vouchers, Advance Payment Etc.
- Maintaining employees database
- Calculating salary statement for employees and co-ordinating with ESI & EPF consultant for employee's final EPF settlement.
- Preparing Salary Slip.
- Preparation of JJ Form, Way Bill (Andhra Pradesh), E-Sugam(Karnataka) during material despatch and C-Form activities.
- Sales Tax [VAT] for head office and other branch offices like [Bangalore Karnataka, Chittoor Andhra Pradesh].
- Professional Tax preparation on half-yearly basis, TDS Statement Prepartion on quarterly basis.
- Co-ordinating with Auditors for yearly both Company and Indiviuals IT compliances and all Statutory Compliances on monthly and yearly basis.
- Preparation of MIS Statement on monthly basis.
- Currently looking GST activities for Head Office and Branch Offices [Karnataka & Chittoor].

May 2012 to Jan 2013 Accountant AKAS Medical, Ambattur Chennai

AKAS Medical is an ISO 9001:2000 certified critical care equipment manufacturing company. It manufacture world class Volumetric Infusion, Syringe Infusion pumps, Patient Monitors and Ophthalmology products which are being used in various hospitals and medical institutions throughout India and other South Asian Countries as well.

Roles & Responsibilities:-

- Working in Tally ERP 9 Software,
- Checking BRS, Handling petty cash,
- Preparing stock and debtors statement for bank OD / CC A/c
- Posting payments, receipts, journal and contra entries,
- Preparing cheques
- Reading, monitoring and responding to the email,
- Answering calls and handling queries,
- Liaising with staff, clients, etc.,
- Organising meetings,travel, Writing minutes,Planning and organising events
- Preparing presentations,
- Preparing papers for meetings,
- Managing and reviewing filing and office systems,
- Sourcing and ordering stationery and office equipment

Educational Qualification

S.No	Degree	Board/University	Grade
1.	M.com	Pune	Higher Second Class
2.	B.Com	Pune	I st Class
3.	H.S.C.	Maharashtra	I st Class
4.	S.S.C.	Maharashtra	I st Class

Other Qualification

- Tally ERP 9.0 Professional Course- Archeil Infobiz, Lonavala –Pune
- Career Edge Computer Course NIIT, Lonavala Pune
- Basic Computer Course Infotech Computers, Lonavala- Pune

Personal Details:	
-------------------	--

Name : Mrs. S. Jayasudha

Husband's Name : Mr. V. Sundaraj

Date of Birth : 1st Nov. 1986

Gender : Female

Marital Status : Married

Language Known : English, Tamil Hindi & Marathi

(All Reading, Writing & Speaking)

Religion : Hindu

Nationality : Indian

Declaration:

I hereby declare that the above information furnished are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date:	Your's truly
Place:	(S. Jayasudha)